alright well good afternoon and happy Monday
today I just had my biggest trade of the month and something that
you just don't really see
happen today and it was here on s C K t
and we're gonna break it down this morning we're gonna go through everything
because I thought I was seeing that I was dreaming this morning
well I wasn't dreaming at least it still feels like I was it was crazy
and so it was just you know normal
Monday and it started out kind of slow
and you know it started this morning I had some trades
um I had a little win on AUD I came in at 8:00am and
you know I caught a good play on the pullback to VWAP here you'll see I took a pullback off these past
highs really nice setup
boom boom boom
kind of grindy but you know I took it back into this past Wick
it pulls back I take the entry off the pullback and I get a good 15
cent move a little bit thick but and it still is thick now too
but then I go over we're gonna go through everything
then I go over to what was it
LRHC go over LRHC I played this okay too I'm like okay little bases
just little bases
well 9:00am comes along
and so does s C K t and I cannot
believe this thing just gets squeezing look at this from 30 cents
to 40 to 50 to 60 to 70 80 to a dollar
and I said man I want to play a pullback on this because the daily chart
looked insane
so it pulls back company
announced a North American distribution
agreement with 3 I technologies from for the apple
for the company's apple base scanning solutions and so it finally
gives me a one minute pull back to VWAP and that's where I punch it over a dollar
I punch it at 1:24 for the break of the high of the day over 1:34
and when I tell you I've never seen something so crazy
right after the entry I'll put the recording here too it squeezed
from 1 to 1:50 to 2:00 to 2:50 to 3:00 to three fifty to four
I thought it was glitching
I by the time I even realized what had just happened
I was already taking profits back at 1 80
which you know I can't be too mad about because it was still a beautiful
trade and
well you know I just I just didn't even know what was going on
I had no idea what was happening so I still played this you can see I
ugh 1 minute pullbacks and I just tried to uh
I just raised stops to 1 minute lows
and I had it from 1:20 to 2:50 even after all of that
so it was a beautiful trade hundred percent um but man it popped a
four and and just like that and I just I didn't register it so quick
enough this happened in like 10 seconds
five seconds not even five seconds it was boom boom boom insane
I just never seen something so crazy 230%
in less than five seconds have you ever seen that
you know have you ever seen that it's crazy
and I just have some little base hits
through here I try to play some pullbacks
for the next leg into the open I got out before the bell
because I don't want to get stuck in the halty mess uh but 2 42 2 2 60
then again break
even here on this one and of course I didn't play it after open
which was when this turned into a disaster
wow so it's just one of those things is you keep on
yeah did I get into this expecting this that's
that's what you have to understand is I didn't get into this expecting
a 200% move
and I certainly
didn't get into expecting 100% move I was getting in expecting
let me just get one 40 let me just get one 50 let me just get one 60
certainly was not expecting this so to get that
is unbelievable had some good trades on STKH2 after market
open I don't want to waste
too much time talking about this just because I don't want to overshadow
stkt just the craziness that that was
but SDKH I played to on the break of VWAP
you can see here we had the break of trend from premarket
we got the break of VWAP where I punched it up into the halt
and played it from 4:70 to about 5:45 it wasn't too bad
it was a little bit too crazy for me though so I had to size down step
away also at mtem
a little bit later too with a little Chinese name too
1 2 big candle move up and I try to punch it over the high of day
1:34 to 1:41 it begins to hesitate here off the highs
puts in place this doji it pulls
back and again I see it start to put in place a double bottom off of 1:25 and so I take it
again at 1:29 risking off this past low for the next leg higher and I
thankfully got it we got it from 1:31 all the way to about 1:60
and then of course I took my full exit as it put in place this topping
tail rejection off the high another really nice 30 cent move
now I also had L Z m
H to end off the morning too this also was very nice
a little bit hard to see what I did here on the 1 minute time frame but I'll show you on the 10 second
where it is a little bit easier to see and so there's a lot that goes into this in terms of
the way I'll be trading at least small cap trading
there's a lot of strategy involved when it comes to like
what the majority you're thinking about doing and when there's
that's how you have an edge and so in this I wait for the 10 second pullback off the 9 and V up and I punch it at 1 83 for the next leg and I get it from 1 84 all the way to about 2 12
really happy with it of course took my full profit
after we put in place the double top or the
topping tail off the high
but why this is so important
is I know that people are watching
this there's nothing else moving at the time people are watching
this for the first pullback and it hasn't pulled back yet
so as soon as it pulls back I punch it
for that next leg higher because I knew people were waiting
people are waiting to punch the first pull back and then they're of course they go chasing it over the highs
and you know that's where I get to move from 1 82 to about 2 10
and that's really just the morning
s c k t was the one it's still up 300% right now but what
a crazy way to start the week I could not believe it
could not believe it so I'm curious
let me know if you caught this thing today I'm sure a lot of you did because it was
the only thing really moving in premarket at that time
it was the most obvious stock
so you know it's just it's crazy to see stuff like this that
stuff that you don't ever really
see when's the last time you've seen something like that it's wild
but this is why we place ourselves into a plus
opportunities and naturally over time you catch home runs like this
like I did this morning with sckt I can't
imagine if I would have got some sold up almost to four bucks
that would have been insane
so that's the morning recap the markets
clearly on fire and of course uh well
the same thing that we did last week we're still doing
again this week and so we're just gonna keep on doing that tomorrow too
building off of what we just did today I'm looking forward to it
as always make sure to subscribe for daily content
just like this if you learn a thing or two and make sure to
to grab the 7 day free trial in the description down below
I do have some exciting news too
I got an extra monitor you know I got my six new screens
and I got an extra ultra wide curved
monitor so I'm gonna be giving it away
at some point this month to members
of momentum so make sure to join up grab the free trial
to uh to get entered later this month of course gift you
get your details on that later
as we uh as we move on at the next week but exciting stuff for sure
we'll give that away to to one of you guys at some point uh
throughout August so I'm excited for that
but outside of that I'll see you back tomorrow
morning in the stream or back here for the daily recap
let me go enjoy my day now might be getting a new car after today
haha so we'll see what happens
I'll catch you guys back tomorrow have an awesome blessed
rest of your day and I'll catch you back then